Guide to the Residential College Seminar Program, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Residential College Seminar Program records, 1993-2002; Accession 2007-A-006
  - ES [Ezra Stiles]
    - Metlitzki, Dorothee -CSES/DC 382b, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 342)
    - Metlitzki, Dorothee -CSES/BR 361b, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 343)
    - Milstone, Leonard -CSES 371a, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 344)
    - Milstone, Leonard -CSES/PC 350a, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 345)
  - TC [Trumbull]
    - O'Sullivan, Sean -CSTC 383b (BK), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 346)
    - O'Sullivan, Sean -CC/MC 320b, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 347)
  - BK [Berkeley]
    - Chignell, Andrew -CSBK 312b (TC), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 348)
    - Fortes, Stephan -CSBK 313b (PC), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 349)
    - Fortes, Sthephan -CSES/SY 424b, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 350)
    - Fortes, Stephan -CSMC/SM 404b, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 351)
    - Fortes, Stephan -CSBK 382b, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 352)
  - BR [Branford] no primary seminars
  - CC [Calhoun]
    - Charney, James -CSCC 301a (TC), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 353)
    - Charney, James -CSBR 372a, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 354)
    - Charney, James -CSCC 141b, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 355)
    - Charney, James -CSCC 122b, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 356)
    - Cuero, John -CSCC 303a (TD), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 357)
  - DC [Davenport]
    - Harrison, K. David -CSDC -- Fall, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 358)
    - Harrison, K. David -CSTC 374a, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 359)
  - TD [Timothy Dwight]
    - Alexander, Elizabeth -CSTD 301a (JE), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 360)
    - Ruquist, Rebecca -CSTD 302a (CC), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 361)
    - Kerk, Nancy -CSTD 313b (ES), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 362)
    - O'Donnell, Heather -CSTD 311b (BR), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 363)
    - O'Donnell, Heather -BR/TC 320b, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 364)
  - JE [Jonathan Edwards]
    - Adair, Robert -CSJE 302a (PC), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 365)
    - Fujiwara, Chris -CSJE 311b (ES), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 366)
    - Hirsch, Theodore -CSJE 312b (TD), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 367)
  - MC [Morse]
    - Chambers, Marcia -CSMC 301a (BK), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 368)
  - PC [Pierson]
    - Vare, Robert -CSPC 303a (JE), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 369)
    - Ho, Dien -CSPC 314b (YC), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 370)
    - Ho, Dien -MC/ -Spring, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 371)
    - Ho, Dien -BK/ES -Spring, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 372)
    - Rosen, David -CSPC 311b (DC), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 373)
  - SY [Saybrook]
    - McGill, Lisa -CSSY 303a (SM), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 374)
    - Redshirt, Delphine -CSSY 321a (TD), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 375)
    - Doolittle, Amity -CSSY 313b (DC), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 376)
  - SM [Silliman]
    - Rifkin, Dena -CSSM 302a (BK), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 377)
    - Rizvi, Kishwar -CSSM 381b (CC), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 378)
    - Callan, Jamie -CSSM 312b (CC), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 379)
  - ES [Ezra Stiles]
    - Allen, Brooks & Mark Humowiecki -CSES 310b (BK), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 380)
    - Burt, Stephen -CSES 305a (PC), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 381)
  - TC [Trumbull]
    - Druks, Herbert CSTC 302a (BR), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 385)
    - James, Pearl -CSTC 310b (PC), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 386)
    - Brodhead, Richard -CSYC 310b, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 387)
  - Residential College Seminars [course catalogue] Spring 2002 (Box 9, Folder 388)
  - BK [Berkeley]
    - Cavanaugh, Jack -CSBK 323a (TD), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 389)
    - Harwood, Craig -CSBK 331b (BR), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 390)
    - Havens, Earle -CSBK 330b (CC), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 391)
    - Trever, Stephen -CSBK 332b (SM), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 392)
    - Trever, Stephen -CSSY 312b (BR), 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 393)
  - BR [Branford]
    - Lanford, Catherine -CSBR 324a (TC), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 394)
    - Austin, Nancy -CSBR 380b (ES), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 395)
  - CC [Calhoun]
    - Anderson, Michael -CSCC 330b, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 396)
    - Marcus, David -CSCC 331b (TD), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 397)
  - DC [Davenport]
    - Keitner, Chimene -CSDC 322a (TD), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 398)
  - TD [Timothy Dwight] no primary seminars
  - JE [Jonathan Edwards]
    - Preuss, Evelyn -CSJE 321a (ES), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 399)
    - Landau, Joseph -CSJE 331b (SY), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 400)
    - Reynolds, Gabriel -CSJE 330b (MC), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 401)
  - MC [Morse]
    - Rachlin, Nahid -CSMC 320a (BK), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 402)
    - Rachlin, Nahid -CSTD 372a, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 403)
    - Rachlin, Nahid -MC/PC -Spring, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 404)
    - Rachlin, Nahid -CSJE/TC 374a, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 405)
    - Rachlin, Nahid -CSDC/CC 352a, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 406)
  - PC [Pierson]
    - Suter, Lindsay -CSPC 323a (MC), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 407)
    - Suter, Lindsay -CSMC 373a, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 408)
    - Atuahene, Bernadette -CSPC 332b, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 409)
    - Davis, Amanda -CSPC 331b, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 410)
    - Gralla, Howard -CSPC 330b (JE), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 411)
    - Gralla, Howard -CSPC 291b, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 412)
    - Gralla, Howard -CSPC 257b, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 413)
    - Gralla, Howard -CSPC 191b, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 414)
    - Gralla, Howard -CSPC 219b, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 415)
    - Gralla, Howard -CSPC 144b, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 416)
    - Gralla, Howard -CSPC 119b, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 417)
  - SY [Saybrook]
    - Schneider, Robert -CSSY 320a (SM), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 418)
    - Baum, Ken -CSSY 330b, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 419)
    - Baum, Ken -CSCC 311b (SM), 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 420)
  - SM [Silliman]
    - Fordham, Douglas -CSSM 322a (PC), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 421)
    - Overmeyer-Velazquez, Mark -CSSM 323a (BR), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 422)
    - Grant, Richard -CSSM 332b (BK), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 423)
    - Raff, Sarah -CSSM 331b (SM), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 424)
  - ES [Ezra Stiles]
    - Austin, Nancy -CSES 320a (DC), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 425)
  - TC [Trumbull]
    - DiPietro, Loretta -CSTC 320a (TD), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 426)
    - DiPietro, Loretta -CSTC 380b (DC), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 427)
    - DiPietro, Loretta and Michael Merson -CSDC/TC 360b, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 428)
    - Suzuki, Yuka -CSTC 323a (CC), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 429)
    - Wilson, Kristina -CSTC 330b (DC), 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 430)